introducing and interviewing the one and
only Joe.
I believe we're on.
We're on.
Good day, Joe.
How are you?
The one and only Joe.
Getting there. No, there's
there's three, isn't there?
I don't know how many.
You keep coming back.
Don't know how many there is. Um before
he starts, I brought this over for Peter
and I just thought I'd give it to him.
This come in from America. give them to
a mate of mine and so on like that and
um sold as giving between 51 to to what
they say 51 to 97%
fuel economy and um so this guy paid up
his money up front and so on. You got to
send your money first. Now this is um
nearly $500 Australian which is
American. What's that? Well, we're 75
cents in the
roughly anyway. So, he got one cent and
it was screwed together. All this top
and screwed on. Everything's jet black
plastic and everything else and so on.
And um
it won't work. It's not blue plastic.
You know, the old blue plastic bucket
and um anyway, so
sorry.
You're right. You can joke as much as
you like. I try to stay serious. I joke
all the time anyway. No worry. Um so he
sent the first one in and and it took
him oh couple of months but finally got
it there and everything else and the um
he put it up to his vehicle and he's um
a mechanic in Lismore and does all the
key cutting got all the analyzing gear
and everything else. So he put on his
vehicle and went for a run to Byron Bay
and back done all the testing and
everything else and found out didn't do
a damn thing. So he thought buckard I'm
going to pull the piece and see what's
in there. And this one here was threaded
there. So he got her in and he undone
her and everything else. And when he
pulled her apart, he found out that that
on the end of it, on the end of those
two fittings down into here is um two
ordinary washers that ramp just ordinary
um you know, nut bolt washers.
What?
Not even stain.
Well, I don't know. Probably Well, it
would be stainless if it was going to
react because the Well, could be. I
didn't didn't check anyway. So, um,
another fellow who been chasing him up
for a tour and talking to him wanted for
a diesel. So, I gave him the same money
and he said, um, you know, um, he'd take
the damn thing and it leaks everywhere
and so on. So, the fells in America who
sold it to him, called him back and
said, "How'd you go with that cell? And
what do you reckon about it? And can we
get you to fill out a paper and
everything else and say, you know, what
you like about everything?" He said,
"This stuff is the biggest hunk of crap
out." She didn't do a damn thing.
Oh, come on. There's there's smaller
hunks of crab and bigger hunks.
So, um within 3 days later,
this one arrived.
Free one. It's all yours.
So, like that. So, I just now gave it to
Peter, but he can pull it to piece and
do whatever he likes, but no good as it
sell. But these things here are out
there all in somebody's name to be sold
and so on. But um and that's all it is
is just black. What's that? Poly
PVC.
4 in 100 mil.
Whatever.
Yep. With end caps. Two end caps.
And the only thing you get is a few
wires.
That's expensive.
And the thing the best bit thing about
it, what changes it from um being
anything else, your brown cell or
anything else is um or hydrogen oxygen
stuff is you don't use costic soda. You
use Drano.
Oh, good. So it's only SAO4.
[Laughter]
So anyway, Peter can have the damn thing
and have pull the pieces and look at
him, put it on and show you all if you
want what's in there. But this is what's
out there and some of the stuff being
sold and it's useless.
Useless.
Right. Anyway,
Joe, now we've got past the real serious
stuff. We on our group called Yahoo
Groups Joe Cell 2 site.
There's been a um an acknowledgement on
some of the Suzuki video
um inquiries.
One of which is if you like, do you want
me to read it out to you so everybody
can hear it? Hi Joe, I hope you are
well. I just wanted to thank you for all
you have done. I truly believe you are
the one who make the greatest difference
in the world. Helping mankind
stop polluting our environment and
slowly killing ourselves with polluting
energy systems. Peter, thanks for
helping Joe get his stuff out into the
public domain. I really do appreciate
you both. To answer your question you
posed in the Suzuki video, I just wanted
to tell you firsthand that I figured out
what you did in the Suzuki Suzuki video
with the Suzuki truck. Joe, you have
reversed the polarity of the entire
system.
Does that require is that's not a
question. That's him telling me.
Told you we were different.
Yeah. So, is that a question?
Well,
is that the end of it,
Joe? You say when you've done what what
you've done is reverse polarity type and
so on. When you shut down the positive
side of the coil, the alternator charges
the system in the opposite direction.
You demonstrated this while in the
restaurant with your fingers. The
alternator is charging this way and your
battery is charging the other way. Later
in the video, you mentioned the Suzuki
truck has a solenoid on the carb and
this was put there to shut down the fuel
from entering the intake manifold. The
solenoid center is positive and the
base.
Yeah. The um to answer all this about
the Suzuki, the Suzuki is out there for
all the use. you know, I'm I'm not a
person doing anything as you know and so
on, but so many people come out there
sort of saying about what Joe's done and
what he's doing and and um
that's better. I can see myself there.
Um
this smart alle with the Suzuki um was
raving that he was a uh
well electronic squirt. Yeah. I can play
with all these and understand all these
things and everything else and so on.
But um not that tipped up of me just I
give
I mean a little short ass but he's down
too far for me.
Um so I just happened to be down down at
this fell's place not working with him
or do anything else and he was
mouththing off about this and that and
everything else all over the place. So I
said yeah you know about cars and
everything. I said I'll go and stuff
yours. So, I just went out and no
screwdrivers, no spanners, no
wait, no anything. And um and just one
little thing and then he couldn't shut
his vehicle. I said, "Well, figure that
one out." So, with all the people out
there and everything else professing
there's so many sites on the internet
about what J cells are and what they do
and everything else, you know, hydrogen
producing machines, everything. That's
Okay. I told Peter and
everything else I'll put him on this.
It's a frequency
frequency that you're changing. Okay.
Vehicles vehicles are known to run like
pre-ignition and cold dieseling and
everything else and the timing's out.
You just change all that to suit and it
brings it back into order. Got a
condenser which is faulty. Car don't go.
So everything else is the same but
condensers out. Any of the electrics or
anything else on a vehicle shut them
down. Okay. So, but what this vehicle
does is probably a few different things
actually. with the Suzuki. Um technology
out there not known so much is um DC
generators. Government took them a long
time ago. Use them in the um uh air
force and everything for sending radio
signals as far as I know around the
world everywhere. And they don't tell
you about them. But early early early
vehicles had DC well you you wouldn't
call them a magneto but that's what they
did call them uh DC magneto. And they
only had one wire coming out of them.
There's no second wire. And that one
wire just went and screwed onto the
engine anyway. And that was from a one
cylinder up to a 12cylinder motor. And
the engines run, right? They just run.
There's no nothing else required. You
don't need distributor or anything else
like that because see, you're doing away
with it. That frequency or whatever else
went into the engine and fired the
engine. See when when people try and
figure out what is actually running the
engine, is it the spark? No, the spark
doesn't fire. The fuel air mix. It's um
visual spark doesn't fire the um the
thing what's occurring and everything
else is that your your um your spark is
jumping from the center electrode over
to ground. And um the spark isn't
igniting anything. It's converting
itself back into uh into the block and
back around through your battery in the
whole circuit. And so
so um
few interruptions, but that's all right.
Um so where does that spark come from?
It comes back to the coil. Okay. And so
your positive and negative going to your
coil
um aren't actually producing.
you're not using any of them. You got to
talk layman's terms. I'm pretty lame.
Um,
bringing it back to the where's this
spark come from? The coil, which is
called a Tesla coil coil in the cars and
everything else is is um it's got a
primary and a secondary winding and
everything. And what happens is is your
your um your negative coming off your
block goes through your point, your
condenser, and then up into your coil
and goes around and comes out the other
side.
as positive. Your positive comes into
the coil, goes around round on the very
early cars and everything else. You goes
round round through your your um primary
and secondary and everything and it
comes out as ground negative. So it's
gone in positive, it comes out negative.
Now you don't use any of them two.
None of them are used up to actually
make the AC spike or comes out the
center of the coil. It is a um it's a
90° spike.
They're there and they create it, but
it's not them that it's actually been
used up to make it. It's check that out.
It's a 90° spike. So, and on Commodore,
it's just given it to you roughly
quickly and everything else. Commodore
has used something called waste spark
management. Ford used it for a while.
Wouldn't pay hold and everything else.
So, then as far as I understand, can't
don't hold me to that one, but Ford had
on for a while and then took it off. But
Commodores use it on their V6s and
everything else where they they use the
positive side as well and fire it. Now
just bring up on the on the running of
the engine, the negative is the thing
which has got the points or the braking
circuit in it for your compression side
of your cylinder. And on the Commodores,
they fire at 6° before top dead center.
So you know up here and they fire and
your piston keeps going and everything
else and then it's explodes down the
cylinder apparently.
So, all right. So, what um uh what the
uh the Commodore motor is is a 350 Chev
motor, right? V8, but two cylinders
missing. So, they don't get real good
economy. So, the Holden and everything
else actually probably for America or
somewhere come up with waste spark
management. If you break that down,
waste spark. Well, they don't have waste
spark. They have waste electricity.
Okay? they're not using it. So they
actually break it like on the negative
side broken by a set of points. They
break the positive side. Now the
positive is a complete opposite to the
negative. So the um the positive side is
then fired into the opposite cylinder
of the the than what the negative one
is. So you have a um two cylinders
coming up at the same time. Okay. One is
under compression
opposite when I look in that mirror
anyway. And that's anyway and um the
sorry because you're in Australia J.
That's it. So the other one coming up is
on exhaust pushing exhaust out. That's
on a four stroke. Okay. So you have your
um exhaust valve open and they fire that
positive. They break the positive side
and they fire that into the exhaust
cylinder at six°. It fires at exact same
time.
Okay, that wasn't exact, but close
enough. So, negative fires a compression
chamber so called and the positive is
fired then into the exhaust at 6° before
top, which actually creates the negative
in the compression chamber creates
explosion, breaks all your gases apart
and gives you, you know, heat and
expansion, everything else. Well, the
other one actually closes down and she
pulls on the piston, the head of the
piston. Even with the valve open, you
got to understand that if you know about
um mechanics and everything else,
two-stroke shouldn't work because the
exhaust is open um first, then your
intake, and it's compressing with the
exhaust. Your color fuel comes in, your
hot gases go out, and it's compressing
with a big open hole. It shouldn't run,
but it does anyway. So um what actually
happens with the Commodores is that
you're getting implosion that the
positive creates an implosion in the
exhaust burn gases and closes them down
creates a pull gives a smoother motor
less miles per gallon that you have to
put in the first part and everything
else. So, we take a motor which is
normally around about the who knows if
it's a really good carbureted one or
something injection one. You might get
15 18 m per gallon out of the original
V8 in a 350 Chev or something. With the
V6,
um you would get probably 20 something,
but they're getting 38 to 40 m per
gallon out of the V6s now because of way
spark. You can go to the computer, cut
that wire, and you break yourself down
to about 20 or so, make your motor run
rougher, noisier, and you still got go,
but you you haven't got the go that
they've got. So, they actually created
this implosion to fire on that
on that side. So, they're using
the um you know, the positive and the
negative. They call it waste spark. Just
come up to date with all that and
everything else, too. you know, check it
out. But, um, and that goes into two
opposite cylinders. So, it double fires,
okay? So, your V6 is really a V12, but
firing on the compression and firing on
the exhaust, and it makes a smooth motor
with good economy and everything else.
Okay? Not many people know about that as
such, but anyway. But your spark coming
out of your coil is a 90° spike. You're
not using the positive or the negative
of your coil. The you're using them
there to set up the field. And when you
collapse one side of the field, you get
that going across. Now, that if you look
at the other tapes while Peter here has
got and everything else on it, that
doesn't seem to have a positive or
negative charge to it. And what we
understand if it had a negative charge
and we know about magnetism and
everything else electromagnetic field
collapsing and whatever else and the
magnetism is what positive the similar
uh repel and the
black poles repel.
Okay. And opposites attract. So if that
spark I've asked people if that spark
was positive coming out of your coil
then it would go to the negative
terminal at your battery in your circuit
but wouldn't go to the positive. But on
the tape you find it going to the
positive and to the negative vice versa.
If it was negative it shouldn't go to
the negative and go to the positive but
it's going to both. And then on top of
it you got a fuel cell there. The
battery is a fuel cell that makes
hydrogen oxygen. They tell you that um
isn't it not even part of the question,
but it's a good understanding so you can
bring up to to start to understand some
of this. They tell you that hydrogen and
all that can be fired in the motor by
that spark.
Your battery produces hydrogen oxygen.
That spark doesn't blow. The battery
doesn't blow. That gets it actually
makes it. If you look at the tapes that
Peter here now has, and the only reason
I give that out there for anybody anyway
is to to see that there's different
frequencies that we don't know of.
There's different things occurring that
we've been told and doesn't occur,
right? And some things do occur when
we're told that they don't occur. Okay,
so really back to it on the Suzuki and
everything else. Yes.
No spanners, no screwdrivers, no nothing
else. But there is a polarity change
and not the way that you understand it.
It's not talk it's not the same talked
about like down at the cafe that was
talking about generators generators with
polarizing them, you know, reverse
polarizing them with the regulator and
everything. Um, this is an alternator
and on the tape it's talking about the
alternator actually well shows you there
the alternator squeal it head off when
we pull the wire off the the positive
for the coil. Not any other time the
motor rev it will go good and everything
else while the keys on and while the
while the positive wires on the coil.
Okay. But you pull the positive wire off
the coil and your alternator how it head
off. And this fellow says, who's on
there? Um, he says that, um, it's the
brand new belt that he put on there that
he No, it's not loose. The one he had on
there before, done it, so he put a brand
new one on there. Put a brand new one
on, tighten it up, and still does it.
Why? Because your alternator is charging
one way and being driven one way. Okay?
And when we pull that wire there and
haven't got to tell you what's actually
running the vehicle then cuz it's not
the alternator and it's not the battery.
Um
it's something called a DC generated
nonregulated frequency. See a regulator
has a generator has a regulator. An
alternator has a regulator.
Okay, we'll get to the next bit of
dozing in a second. the first DC
magnetos or DC generator type with the
one wire never had a regulator
frequency that it produced it didn't
have it.
So when you're trying to comprehend that
as such, try and figure out pre-ignition
and cold dieseling,
okay, pre-ignition, these are only
talking about electric cars, okay, not
diesel vehicles. We're talking electric
petrol driven spark motors at the
moment, okay? There's a couple of
concepts there. What occurs? What people
don't understand our hydraulics. Won't
go there too much, but our our
hydraulics,
they say, scientists and everybody else
says that we have a liquid cannot be
compressed.
Okay? Well, you put a little bit of
water into a diesel motor and everything
else and don't care how fat the conrod
is or the size of the piston, she'll
just smash it to smitherines because
she's 100% hydraulic lock. Okay? Won't
compress. But what actually happens on
electric motor car, okay, you can grab
the garden hose, been shown to use and
everything else. Um, Hitler had it and
everything else, you know, you can take
the flipping water, stick water straight
down the throat, pour it in, turn the
garden hose on and turn it on full ball.
All you got to do is bring the
accelerator up a little bit just to
compensate so it doesn't cut out because
it's right and the water goes in.
It doesn't the amount that you can pour
in there doesn't actually evaporate
and then you can catch it in a bucket
out the exhaust. Okay? It doesn't
evaporate and then condense again in the
time that it's doing it with the revs of
the motor and everything else. You bring
your revs right up. It decodes the
valves, decodes the pistons, unseas the
sticky rings, unseas the sticky valves
and flame just frees the motor. But the
electrics going through that engine
takes away all hydraulics cuz you can
put in there with the motor going right
and you don't get the hydraulic lock.
You turn the engine off, put some water
down there or a liquid or something else
like that and then try and hit the key,
clunk, you don't go anywhere. But if the
engine's going and you put it into
there, it's a different thing happening
all together. So now with the Suzuki, we
not got an offer. We're still there with
the Suzuki and everything else. The key
was turned off. Pre-ignition cold diesel
and what is occurring? Pre-ignition is
we've been told there's too much carbon
on the piston or too much heat or so on
like that in the chamber. Um many things
can cause pre-ignition. too much
compression, too much carbon, too much,
you name it, whatever. But this the
timing, how do you stop the
pre-ignition? So, in pre-ignition, what
you're doing is you're starting your
vehicle and then your motor is supposed
to be hot and you turn the key off. So,
when you turn the key off, your motor
don't stop. It actually starts to not
run smooth. It runs roughish. Okay? So,
I can make your motor run rough. You can
make a motor run rough just by grabbing
the distributor and turn the damn thing
out of where it is now. Okay? And it'll
run rough as guts. Okay? So, the um
pre-ignition can be stopped in an engine
by just retarding the timing. And that's
with the key on.
Okay? Just your timing a fraction
and so on and then turn the key off and
your motor just stops.
So, but if it's too far advanced on the
timing, then she can run on. Doesn't do
it with every engine or anything else.
It just you can make your engines do it
by just advancing advancing too much.
People out there, if you understand
about pre-ignition or if you had it
happen, fine. Your keys turned off. Now,
if your keys turned off, you've also
shut down a few other things. One is if
you got a carburetor, you shut down the
um electronic, you know, the the
solenoid. Okay. Solenoid, which is
virtually double wiring, you know,
electromagnetic field, and that actually
throws a um piece of metal. Either
throws it out because of the way that
you wound it and she pushes across the
hole and and shuts down the engine.
Okay. Stops fuel going. The Cortisas and
Geminis and everything else actually
have it the other way winding and so on.
It actually pulls up, pulls away. So,
it's pulling into it. So you got push
out and pull in. That's a solenoid.
Okay. So you shut down your positive,
you shut down your solenoid. You shut
down the fuel. You're supposed to shut
down the engine. But people are turning
their engines off with solenoids and
they're turning off the coil.
Or are they turning off the coil and so
on, which is your ignition spark
positive.
And the engines are still going
running rough as guts. Okay. So, and
that's with the key turned off. You got
to start asking yourselves what is
actually happening when your engine is
going by either your generator or your
alternate and everything else and you
turn the key off. Have you shut down the
spark?
No, you haven't. You shut down the
forward spark and then your dash light
comes on. Okay? Because you're feeding
the other way and it's not the same
spark. It's not the same thing all not
even the same flaming stuff. Anyway, so
um and the car goes so you haven't got
your solenoid, you haven't got your coil
and you haven't got your ignition, but
your car is still running.
Okay, so why is it running? Well, what
I've done in the past and everything
when it's pre-ignite and everything
else, I don't go and I can on my can I
don't go always I do for other people,
but turn the distributor backwards,
the timing and turn your key on
and run it that way. Okay? Because you
out here, your car will rust too. Okay?
Because we're running a negative earth.
So called here, England runs a positive
earth. Their bodies don't rust. They
don't use butterfly chokes to shut down
air. They use flooding chokes. If they
use a choke, all they still all their
cars hop in, turn a key, press a button,
boom, in all the wet weather. They're
putting because of sleet and snow and
and everything over the roads in
England. What they throw on the roads?
Salt.
Well, you put salt on the road out here
and drive your car around for a long
while. What are you going to have?
Rusted out seat.
Another rust bucket.
Rust bucket.
Well, in England they run that system
which is a positive earth as such and
everything else and that stops the
rusting of the bodies and so on like
that. Okay. And gives better start and
don't need to reduce in the winter time.
They don't need to reduce the air to
give you more fuel so you don't splutter
and cough and backfire up through the
carby and everything and drive down the
road. They run positive earth. We stupid
out here. We run negative earth and
everything else and so on. And then our
bodies rust. We get static electricity
in our vehicles. And now we need a in
winter when a cold weather and we need a
butterfly choke to shut off the air to
give ourselves more fuel. Isn't that
good? Really good.
You know, it's good for the oil company
anyway. So, and all these different
things occur because of it. So,
that's pre-ignition. we can the
timing. What I do is on what I've done
on the vintage cars and on some of the
others is I don't do that. I turn the
key off and if it's pre-igniting, I keep
advancing it because what you're going
to find is there's only a degree in
where those motors will fire and if
that's with the key turned on within
that degree there's top dead center and
you got your circle and and it fires
within that degrees on this side. It's
backwards on there. It's a tape but here
to me on that side. say 6° before top
dead center because there's top dead
center, piston's coming up, fires on
that side. Okay. So, if it's firing
there and so and you turn the key off,
where is your actual spark or frequency
going?
It's gone over somewhere else.
It's put your timing out.
So, why won't your engine run with the
key turned off?
It has got frequency spark there. It
has, but it's completely reversed
because the engine's gone. It's complete
reverse and it's put the timing over to
another place. What I do is I advance a
distributor.
Okay? And what happens is you go,
it starts running smooth. And then you
can accelerate with the key turned off.
It's with the engine going. You'll
figure out how to start it otherwise and
what to do otherwise, but that's what I
do. And it actually runs. But if you
want it to run properly with a key on
and you turn the key off and it stops,
you have to the distributor. So
what now is the other cold dieseling?
Okay, cold dieseling is not a diesel
engine. Cold dieseling is an engine
which is actually you start it when the
motor's cold and you turn it straight
back off again and the damn thing
pre-ignit or not pre-ignit, cold diesel
is what they call it. It's not
pre-igniting cuz it's hot. It's now cold
and it runs on. Dam.
Okay. So, is that okay?
All those things. It's good. Right
north. Anyway, um so
if you did it tomorrow, Joe, we might
win the cup.
That's it. Not into it. Um so, um the
cold easing is cold engine. Turn the key
off. She keeps going. That's electric
shutdown. That's ignition to the
positive side of the coil shut down and
whatever else shut down. Fuel pumps and
everything else if you want to look at
it. The engine keeps going but runs
rough. So, how do you stop that?
You turned your key off. Have you shut
down the SP? What's making the motor
run?
To stop your coal dieseling, what do you
do? You have to advance your distributor
because it's too far It's gone
out of that. What's gone out of that
when you turn the key off?
Okay. So, you have to bring your
distributor up a little bit ahead,
advance it a bit, and then you can start
your car and turn it off. And she just
goes and stops. Why is the damn thing
running
when you turn the key off and everything
else you shut down? Why is it still
going?
Um, when the timing is gone one way or
the other. Okay. Now, on the Suzuki, we
haven't gone from it. What we got is a
whole lot of things here people haven't
figured out what has really taken place
with the Suzuki. Now, I didn't say I was
going to tell you every single thing
here. I'm just bringing up a little bit
onto something because see, you tell
everybody everything and what do you
get?
You call the
They still wouldn't know, Joe.
Yeah, understand. So,
um you don't you don't get any praise
and glory and I don't want it anyway.
And you don't make yourself out to be
anything. In fact, you got all everybody
out there who want to write about you
call you a flipping idiot. Right. And
then there's other people here like this
guy here. Appreciate his views and
everything else, but doesn't do anything
for me. Sorry about that, but I don't
don't care about praise and glory and
I'm not interested on what you think as
such. And I'm not doing it. I'm not
doing it for anybody or any reason or
anything. It's just and I said to Vita,
you put it out there and all it's about
is that all these things written about
Joe and everything else. Uh he never put
any of them up there and they're all
been crossfusing all this flipping
information everywhere and and getting
it all out of whack. It's frequencies.
It's not gases. It's not petrols. It's
not anything like that. It's
frequencies. What cars do I found out
how you can make cars run without that?
Peter Brock, same problem. Pet now dead.
Someone like that. pity for him. But
anyway, Peter had a car run without the
fuels and people thought he was running
a fuel polarizer. Wasn't a fuel
polarizer. He ran out of fuel three laps
earlier. Fuel polarizers work with fuel.
Everybody thought they don't think, you
know, they just accepted what was told
to him. But Peter has run an air
polarizer.
That's what he's
okay. So that himself and everything
else run without fills and stuff.
Doesn't matter. I mean the Japanese know
the car companies know it happens to
them. Pre-ignition, cold dieseling, all
these effects that they run different
metals in engines. They get all these
things happen and they don't want to
tell you and they don't want to give it
to you and they don't want you to know
and the science doesn't tell you about
any of this stuff as well and everything
else and we don't actually think about
what's taking place. The Suzuki again
back to it. Suzuki with a key turned off
and so on like that doesn't pre-ignite
and doesn't coal diesel.
Why? Well, distributor hadn't been
touched. The frequency in the
distributor, the distributor is not
turned. It's doing what it's supposed to
do. It is not too far advanced, and it's
not too far It's where it's
supposed to be. Okay?
And I reverse polarity, but not a normal
polarity. And I didn't have a spanner or
a screwdriver or anything else to do it.
It took one wire. That's one that you
are going to have a look at. Not me. Cuz
I'm not telling you the why. Not yet.
You look at it. And what it did is that
when the car is going, what you seen on
the on the disc of tape or whatever
else, the alternator is fighting itself
crazy because the alternator is binding
up the fan belt, squealing crap is out
of the fan belt because the alternator
doesn't want to go in the direction. I
say it's going in the opposite
direction. The alternator does not want
to go in the direction that that fan
belt is going, which is connected to the
crankshaft. And that's why it's only
howling when we either turn the key off
or pull that wire at the um at the yeah
coil.
Okay.
All right. Breaking all down everything
else. Got to ask use a few other
questions and you'll come up to what it
is. What is a coil? Okay. It's called a
Tesla coil. It's got a primary and a
secondary and so on like that. And uh
yeah, your windings. What's in the
middle of those windings?
nothing. So what did what did Tesla
find? He found out if you don't do that
and everything else and you drive these
two fields to it and you collapse one
side of the fields and everything, you
get not a DC DC, you get an AC spike
coming out. Now the DC might have a
positive or negative charge to it or the
the positive may have a positive or
negative charge to it. But that one out
the center at 90°, what has it got? you
you check that out yourself. Okay? If it
had either either one, it would not go
to one or the other on the battery or
the fields in the engine if it's a
magnetic field. And that's what it says
it is. It's collapsing electromagnetic
field. Okay?
So, and if it goes to both, you figure
out why and how and and what it is.
Okay?
If you can't, maybe some other time I'll
tell you. But
so you can use either side of the coil
and everything else. So the coil doesn't
have a piece of metal in the middle.
What is a solenoid?
Solenoid does have a piece of metal in
the middle. It's got the two windings
and everything else. Sets up
electromagnetic field. If it's got a
piece of metal in there, she'll either
push out of its round push, you know,
wound one way or pull in if it's wound
the other. Okay, good. Now we break
ourselves down to a generator. What is a
generator?
Generator is um setting up the windings
and so on. So, it looks exactly the same
way that it's wound as the coil or
anything else, but you got your two your
positive and your negative. And what's
in the middle? You got a circular piece
of something in there. Now, if you turn
it by the motor, you get electricity out
of it. What happens if you drive
electricity into it? Well, you haven't
got a generator. you've got yourself a
starter motor.
Okay? Because now putting electricity to
it actually turns
the generator. So your generator now
it's a starter motor. So what's a
starter motor? Starter motor's got your
two windings and everything else. And
when you throw power at it, she turns
the the shaft and everything. Now if you
um if you got an English type starter
motor, you got a bending spring on the
end and she will actually wind up and
everything and throw back in by a spring
load. If you've got yourself one of what
we have on all our normal cars and
everything else, we need to apply two
things on here. Now, one is a solenoid
and the starter motor. So, you got two
sets of coilings, positive and
negatives, to do two different things.
One is the starter shaft turns, doesn't
throw out, doesn't pull in, doesn't
throw a spike.
That looks for another reason. Now the
um
so you spin it by throwing power at it.
Okay. And the um and the starter mode is
the same in England and Australia.
Either negative earth or positive earth
doesn't make any difference. Still
turns. Okay. So you put a solenoid on.
So your starter turns and then your
solenoid pushes and throws that rod out.
Okay. And that engages into the
flywheel. And um she actually starts to
turn the flywheel.
You may not have picked it up as such
and everything else on the tape is what
actually happens
to a starter motor.
When the starter motor is being taken
past
the spinning ability on what you can
drive it with by the power what's in the
vehicle. Uh, in other words, the battery
the battery will spin the starter motor
at a certain speed.
If it's 6V, it spins it at so many
revolutions. If it's 12 volts, similar
thing and everything. What happens if
you stick 12 volts onto a 6V starter
motor?
What happens if you stick 6 volts onto a
12 volt starter motor?
Okay, you understand? Like a flat
battery.
So, what happens if you take a starter
motor and spin it faster than what the
original flame electricity pouring
through and around your circuits and
everything else actually does
while it's locked in. It's been driven
by the solenoid. Lock it into the into
the uh ring gear. And when you let the
key go and everything else at a certain
revolution, does your ring gear throw it
back out? Not at high speed.
She wants to keep throwing itself
forward. And if you got a reverse
polarity and everything else, which
isn't that's that's not where I done it.
Sorry, it's not where I done it. But
what happens with the starter motor when
you over spin and pass the point? What
have they become?
Generator.
Generating what?
that other type of frequency
which isn't regulated.
And where does that go?
Well, see, it doesn't come up the wires
and it doesn't go down the wires.
Goes through the body of the the starter
and energizes the engine.
It goes out through the shaft and ends
up as a DC generator. I don't have DC
magneto. No, I can't call that either.
It sets up an unregulated
DC field what goes through into the
flywheel up the crankshaft.
Yeah. And there's a possibility, there's
a big possibility that that actually can
do the same as the DC Magneto in the
early days that they don't want you to
know about, which is sending a field
into the engine. What doesn't use that
kind of spark to actually it's not spark
frequency to fire the engines because
the spark does not fire the engine.
You don't think so? How do you check a
folly spark plug? Getting into it real
fast. Folly spark plug. You know, don't
care about anything. We're going to miss
faulty spark plug. Okay. Well, without
pulling it out. Okay, I'm not saying one
like some other strange weird people who
they can have a look at this. Grab a
good brand new spark plug and drive the
end of the flaming tip down onto the
center electrode and think you got a
faulty spark plug. No, no, that's a dead
short. The only thing that will happen
there is that your coil will jump spark
straight out of the center electrode
down onto the negative side because your
points are on that side. should jump
straight down out of the center onto the
negative electrode.
Okay? If it's negative earth and
negative side that you're breaking
because it's got nowhere to go, it can't
go down there. But in a spark plug which
is fully carboned up or something like
that or cracked and it's a different
happening down there through the carbon
or something like that. So, she's not
getting the right frequency to fire your
engine by the spark. How do you prove
that it's a fully spark plug? outside
the engine.
Grab your spark plug lead. There's a
spark plug. And there's your lead. And
you go on, it's missing. Take it away.
It's missing.
Make the spark visibly jump in front of
you outside the engine. What happens?
Now, they tell you that what you're
doing just building up charge and
everything else. So, it's going to jump
in there. It's dead shorted in there
through the carbon. It's not going to
spark. You've got your spark jumping out
here. So, what's happening at the end of
the spark plug,
you set up a different frequency
and you're not using the spark to
actually fire the petrol and air, but
you prove that you got a faulty spark
plug. So, you pull that spark plug out
and you throw it away and then you stick
the lead on and now the motor goes h
with the spark there, but it was going h
without the spark there before the spark
was outside.
something to think about. Okay. So, what
is that frequency that actually made the
motor run without the spark inside the
cylinder? Or if it does have a spark
inside the cylinder, if it does, and I'm
wrong, right? If I'm wrong on that, then
what sparks outside and what sparks
inside? Is it not the same? They're not
the same.
And then if you really knew and could
find that out and everything else,
there's a possibility that you could use
that frequency and throw away your
distributor and spark plug leads and
spark plugs and everything else and run
your engine on that.
Joe, can we get rid of the motor?
Um, Freddy Fl used to cut a hole in the
floor and use his feet, but he didn't go
to, you know, calluses, I suppose. I
don't Could you use a a different sort
of uh um energy into the actual
transmission?
You mean just to drive the gearbox?
Yeah.
Well, they're doing that with electric
motors.
Just with electric motors, right?
And they're using electric and hybrid
cells and things like that.
Could you spin the cell in if if that
were the the unit or can you
cell? What's it what do you call a cell?
Well, just I don't know whatever it
sounds.
I'll let you get with it. You know,
that's a strange question. I don't know
what he's really asking and such. But
yeah, you can get rid of engines. People
have um run different things in, you
know, behind the electric motors or so.
They only understand that as such. Um
gear ratio, I don't know, pedal cars,
pedal things, whatever you want to do
use. But I think we're going a bit
backwards now. People want to go fast.
People don't want to go back and
reinvent the wheel.
Um
there are many many ways of doing it and
everything else. But anyway, so let's
let's finish what's actually happened.
There is one little tiny thing that took
me about 3 seconds without a spanner or
a screwdriver. It's 3 seconds underneath
the bonnet of the car which does these
things. Okay. And so far, nobody's been
able to roughly figure out or even come
smoothly figure out what's happened. And
it has. To start with, it is reversing
the polarity to some degree, which isn't
one that we know of because it's
fighting the alternator and it's
fighting everything else. When we bring
the revs up on the Suzuki, you'll find
out that your normal spark, which is in
your spark plug leads and everything
else, disappears. So your motor runs
smooth up higher and you lose the spark
from your coil
distributor points condens condenser and
everything else. Why we got that spark
there? Yeah. Well, when things are
missing off the uh coil and there is a
condenser which is going from the
positive side of the coil. It's not a
condenser. It is but we call it a
suppressor. Okay, suppressor. If we want
to look at a suppressor and a condenser,
the same things, primary and secondary
as such. And what happens if we want a
condenser for our spark? We hook it up
on the negative side of our coil without
points and she goes through and makes
the car run. If it's faulty, right, you
pull that out, unscrew the case off the
body and everything. You could pull your
car at 1,000 mph. You won't get a kick
out of it with all the spark. Everything
else spark there won't kick. Okay.
What's a suppressor? Well, the
suppressor is earth ground outside case
the same as condenser
and the condenser goes to the negative
side. Suppressor goes to the positive
side of the coil
and takes away the crackle out of your
wireless and everything else. you know
what comes from your static out of your
alternator or out of your coil or out of
your your leads and everything else
because of this jumping, vibrating,
pulsing feel that really isn't even
needed because it's jumping across the
center electrode in your spark plug back
down to ground to try and give you a
flatline
uh frequency.
So your everything that we know of
um doesn't run on AC.
Now, you can put AC to it, but doesn't
run on the AC. Your um your TV um has to
convert back to DC to turn it on. Your
video DC to turn it on. Your wireless DC
to turn it on. Your computer DC to turn
it on. Your jug has to go with the
coiling and everything else back to DC.
You don't think it's DC? AC will kill
you, kick you, knock you right over.
One, two, three coils in the jug element
and everything in the water. Put your
hand in, turn it on. and she'll just
boil water. She won't kill you cuz it's
converted through a coil back to a DC.
Okay. All these things work through DC.
Your engine works off DC frequency.
Doesn't work off AC. The spark plugs
there to jump the spark across to
convert it back to a DC flatline charge.
So, it'll flame and fire the engine.
And um and some of the early early cars
never had them. They never had the
points, never had the condensers, never
had the fame and spark plugs, never had
distributors, never had leads. Okay. And
um Maggis and all that. Well, they had
the advantage of Maggie, your frequency
spark, which they did do. They did have,
you know, a breaking very big whacking
flaming AC kick to them. Okay? But then
they had to use spark plugs. But go back
before that, they didn't. And back
before that, they didn't. Okay? You had
all these different vehicles like um you
heard of petrol KO cars, you know, start
them on petrol, turn them over to Kero.
Then they had Kerry, not knowing too
much about Kero water. Start them on KO
warming up and everything else. Turn
them over on the water and drive all day
on water. Don't want you to have that
one either. Okay. Um you know, in the
war when they didn't have petrol, so
many ideas come out if you want to chase
them up. So many so many ideas come out.
Look at um a charcoal burner. Okay, we
got ones driving around here all the
time. Charcoal burners. No fuel. Well,
they don't got old charcoal. Burned up
carbon and everything else. Reheat the
damn thing. And the only thing you can
say is going in the engine. It's not a
fuel. It's not a gas. It's not anything
else. It's re burnt or reheated up
charcoal. And for some reason, it's
putting out a frequency that makes your
motor run.
Already burnt away stuff. all these
fellow scientists and everything come up
with an idea that it reproduced a new
gas or something else like that. Fine.
Well, if it did and you've already
exhausted all your burnt stuff and
everything, why can't they make you that
gas to run the engine? Is it hydrogen?
Is it oxygen? Is it methane, alcohol?
What is it? I don't know. You go back
and check it. But it's just burnt stuff
that also um
doesn't matter. Just just look at some
of the concepts.
So, there's a couple of things happening
with the Suzuki. Couple of things. First
of all, um we are repolarizing and using
a different frequency to actually fire
the engine down low speed. That's with
the key turned off and on and it's no
pre-ignition needed, no cold dieseling
needed, and it doesn't do the blah blah
blah bl because the distri timing is
right and this frequency lines up into
that to work it out anyway. Okay? And if
you don't think there's anything going
through your coil and everything else
and so on like that, well, should
rethink it, okay? Because you only
really needing any electricians or
anything else here out there, they say
you need an opposite.
Well, they tell you you need two wires
or two connections. You go and look at
Christmas tree lights. They don't have
two. You might plug it in one end here
and take it around the other end and
plug it in the opposite charge there.
But that means that two things are
running two different ways up one wire.
Okay? One's positive, one's negative if
it's the case. Or both are negative or
both are positive. Positive plus,
positive minus. There's all these
different things you can play with and
figure out and what's out there you're
not told. Okay? Not learned, not they
don't want you to know as such. people
keep finding them and everything else
again and they think they found
something wonderful and and maybe Tesla
found it, maybe these other guys found
it and everything else and they just
shut it all down and don't teach anybody
and then they hide all the info and you
have to stumble across it again or
somebody does.
But these things are occurring naturally
in cars
naturally.
And all I've done is I've played with
these things. Not very much. Played with
them, found out about them, and used
them.
So the Suzuki used a reverse polarity to
start with, but then it tapped into
something else. When the revs come up,
we dropped out the frequency, the spark,
the everything by the no spark, the
spark plug in. So what was running? The
engines were running rather well in
smooth and quiet. We don't
except it was noisy. The engine's got
tappers.
Yeah. No. And the that belt on the
alternator was squealing. Joe,
I understand that. I already explained
that.
Yeah.
The thing is that the um the alternator
is fighting. So, you're not running off
the battery and you're not running off
the alternator. What you are running off
when we get up in revs is we're
transferring over and the starter motor
becomes a generator by being turned
faster than it can can normally be and
it's outputting and it doesn't output
back up through the wires where a
generator outputs which then has to be
regulated. The damn thing goes out
through the center turning shaft. A way
that they don't even think of. But see,
that's what a coil does. Car coil goes
out through the center of your wirings.
Not in and out. There goes out a
different direction. 90° spike. Same
thing happens on the starter motors when
you wind them up too far and they end up
with a new energy, a new frequency, a
new spark, a new can't call the spark
because there's no spark and it's not
being cut. It's not being pulsed. It's
just a 100% flat line. And if you want
to feel it with your hand, you're not
going to feel it because you can't feel
DC. The only way you can feel DC is if
you foam and pulse it or turned off and
on. She goes She's not
flatline. Okay. So,
um
in in the car runs and what I done, you
work out any of the other fellows out
there just for the present.
You go out and um you figure out what I
touched and what I done in 3 seconds
flat because I can go back to these
fellows going. He still can't turn it
off. He still can't stop the damn thing
right now.
I was driving him nuts, haven't you?
Yesterday I was down there again and
everything else and he's still been
driven nuts because he's still stuffed
on how to do anything
and he wants to sell that vehicle too
the way it is.
He he told me yesterday that he found
something else out. He found out another
way to shut down the engine that he
didn't know how to shut it down before.
He said this is how electronically mind
it is and if he gets his tape it doesn't
matter. I'm not trying to run him down
or anything else. It's just we all there
and me included are all under some
stories and we don't understand
every single thing. We're not all smart
asses. All right. Some things we haven't
learned or know about yet. So I can't
say him say or call him that. He just
doesn't understand. Solenoid. Okay. He
didn't even know what the name of it was
on the carburetor to shut down the fuel
when you turn your key off and to the
that wire. He said, "I found another
wire. It goes to that thing on the
carburetor. You know that round thing
with
I said, "Yeah, call the solenoid."
Yeah, call solenoid. He said, "Yeah, if
I take that off with the key and
everything else and so on like that."
And so, and he said, "If I ar that out
to the body," he said, "the engine
stops."
I said, "That's a positive power going
to that wire." And I said, "The the
engine is negative." I said, "You ar
that out? You got dead short through
your whole system."
I said, "So wonder it didn't blow fuses
and everything." He said, "Well, it did
actually at first." And he said, "I had
to bypass the fuses.
That's good. So, next time he does, and
it sticks that way, his car is going to
burn." But he found out to stop the
engine.
So,
anyway, can we um
we got another question?
Well, that's one question
and we've only got 10 to go, Joe.
No, probably don't. It'll cover a hell
of a lot of the questions. It's going to
get fascinating.
Okay, you ready?
There's something on the net at the
moment called the inventor runs an
engine on proton cells.
Never heard of a proton.
Okay. Do you know BJ?
No.
Never heard of BJ. The guy from Bunder.
Yeah. Well, I thought it might have been
John. Um, Beam Beams of Jin. Yeah.
Hey BJ, JB, you know, have it with cola.
Lost me.
Sorry, Jim. Bean.
No.
An alcoholic drink.
Maybe should be into it. Jeff,
my brain's screwed enough without
getting into alcohol.
There's a chat from Bundberg. He says he
knows you, been doing a lot of work with
you.
How many people out there know me? How
many people do I remember?
I'm lucky to remember what day it is.
Okay, good.
Let alone how many people have come past
me? How many people have ranged me up?
How many people have sent me stuff off?
Very, very quickly, the University of
New South Wales,
uh, did they run a 1976 Land V8 on the
bench for months with no radiator?
No. What they had? Well, I who
the University of New South Wales?
No, they um don't know. All I do know is
there's mixed up information as far as I
know and everything else. original rover
and everything else was taken from a
professor who sort of now has passed on
too and so on. We won't run him down too
much and so on, but
he um he told he told um he went and
showed this vehicle to the RTA in
Newcastle and everything else and done
all these tests and so on like that on
it. And then the RTA apparently one of
the guys there fronted out his place and
wanted to get into doing it with him and
everything else. And then the vehicle
sort of went missing and the Victorian
government, as far as we know, ended up
with the engine out of the car. And
I seen it once and I've heard about
other people seeing it and being there
and everything else. She's out of the
car with no batteries, no exhaust, no
radiators, no nothing else. And they
can't shut her down. There's no fuel on
board. There's no They can't stop it.
There's not even a cell on board and
they can't stop it. They've got cameras
and everything else into the cylinders
taking shots of in they still don't know
what it's running on. That's the last I
heard about that years ago. Something's
flashing on the thing.
All right. Okay. We got one minute or so
to go, Joe.
Okay. So, no.
Joe, have you received numerous death
threats?
Not lately. No. No. Come on. I'm not
scared. I'm not in for you. I'm not in
Only me. Big bastard.
Bigger they are, the harder they fall.
Um, no. No, no. People have said out
there that um you I've been threatened
and I'm in, you know, hiding and all
that. That's crap. I stopped doing
things cuz I chose to stuff anybody
else. Okay. I got threatened to send me
kids back in the post. It's written in
Nexus years ago and everything else. I
chose not to have kids sent back in the
post if I went ahead and showed Beyond
2000 and new and um Nexus and everything
else this um all this technology. So, I
just said, "No, sorry. Not coming."
Because that's what's going to happen to
me kids. That's what I was threatened
with. And I don't need these threats. I
don't want them. I didn't do it for that
reason. So, stuff stuff everybody. I
don't care. Don't matter.
Right. Well, just
wait for that tape to run out.
No, no, it won't run out, Joe.
It won't. Good.
No, no,
Joe. Thanks very much for um answering
the one question. As I said, we've only
got 10 10 questions, nine to go.
You going to change the tape?
I want to copy this stuff the way it is.
Don't cut that bit off either. There
certain people out there I've allowed to
do things. Don't don't
do the right thing. They just don't give
me they don't come back. They don't do
the right thing. You know, they don't
give me what they steal. They don't give
me what they flame it.
You can't steal it and give it back to
you. That's That's true. How this not
stealing?